// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
const contentString = "3";
const qsup = contentString.sup();

let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "If  a.b = 12, a and b are positive numbers. What is the maximum value of a + b-1?",
    answer: "D. 12",
    options: [
      "A. 6",
      "B. 7",
      "C. 8",
      "D. 12"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: `If x${qsup} -8=19 then the value of 3x${qsup} is..`,
    answer: "C. 81",
    options: [
      "A. 51",
      "B. 72",
      "C. 81",
      "D. 97"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "In a class, there are 10 students who have an average score of 65. If you add the scores of the other 5 students, their average becomes 70. What is the average score of these five students?",
    answer: "C. 80",
    options: [
      "A. 70",
      "B. 75",
      "C. 80",
      "D. 85"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "If  x=0,13  and  y =0,12 the value of (x+y)(x-y)=",
    answer: "B. 0,0025",
    options: [
      "A. 0,002",
      "B. 0,0025",
      "C. 0,025",
      "D. 0,035"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "S+M = 21 grams. M+L = 56 grams. If Yoga weighs 2 L-sized containers together, the mass of the two containers is... grams",
    answer: "B. 84",
    options: [
      "A. 79",
      "B. 84",
      "C. 77",
      "D. 95"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "LCM from two prime numbers x and y is 14. With x>y, the value of 3x-y is…",
    answer: "B. 19",
    options: [
      "A. 13",
      "B. 19",
      "C. 21",
      "D. 23"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "(1532)(1532)-(1524)(1540) equal to?",
    answer: "D. 64",
    options: [
      "A. 8",
      "B. 16",
      "C. 32",
      "D. 64"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "2 times x to the power of 3 equals to 54, what is the value of x",
    answer: "C. 3",
    options: [
      "A. 1",
      "B. 2",
      "C. 3",
      "D. 4"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "The ratio of the radii of circle A to B is 5 : 6. What is the ratio of the two times  area of ​​circle A to B?",
    answer: "B. 25 : 36",
    options: [
      "A. 5 : 6",
      "B. 25 : 36",
      "C. 36 : 25",
      "D. 50 : 72"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "There is a triangle ABC with a right angle at B. The length of side AB is equal to 0,96. The length of side BC is equal to 0.28. What is the length of the side AC?",
    answer: "B. 1",
    options: [
      "A. 0.8",
      "B. 1",
      "C. 1.2",
      "D. 2"
    ]
  }

];